allthingsceleb.com 2016-06-25

# Privacy Policy – All Things Celeb

BVJ4 Enterprises, Inc. (“We” or “Us”), the owner of www.allthingsceleb.com (the “Website”), may revise and change this policy and the ways in which we collect, use and disclose personal information provided by users of the Website (“You” or “Your”). Please check back here frequently to review the latest version of this policy.

**Introduction**

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose and transfer the information you provide when you interact with the Website or features of the Website such as downloadable applications, games, advertisements and surveys. We respect the privacy of everyone who uses the Website.

By accessing or using the Website, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Website, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service http://www.allthingsceleb.com/terms (“Terms”), including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. The Terms are incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy or the Terms, please do not use the Service.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, process, and store your personal information. The information we may collect is described in Section 1 (What Information We Collect About You), and may include data related to account setup and security, such as your name and email address, and other data you may choose to provide, such as your gender, address, additional email addresses, telephone number, occupation, education, and hobbies (collectively, the “Personal Information”).

In this Privacy Policy, we will address:

  * What Personal Information We Collect About You
  * How We Use the Personal Information We Collect
  * How We Share the Personal Information We Collect
  * Third-Parties
  * Third-Party Links
  * User Content
  * Security of Your Personal Information
  * Access to Your Personal Information
  * Do Not Track Signals and Minors
  * Contact Us
  * Changes to This Policy

1\. What Information We Collect About You

We may collect Personal Information directly from you, from third parties, or automatically through your use of the Website.

**_Information We Collect Directly._**

  * The Website may require you to register for an account to access additional features of the Website (the “Additional Features”). In the event that registration is required to access the Additional Features, we may require you to provide us with your first and last name and your email address.
  * If we offer Additional Features, you may elect to provide information to us regarding your physical address, birthdate, additional email addresses, telephone numbers, gender, occupation, education, and hobbies.
  * Should you choose to directly contact us via email, we will collect your name and any contact information you may provide us with, such as your email address, telephone number or mailing address.
  * We require you to provide us with necessary transaction information, such as your address and payment information, if you purchase a product or service from us.

**_Information We Collect Automatically._**

  * We automatically collect analytic information related to how users use the Website on an aggregate and anonymous basis.  We may use Google Analytics to collect this information.

**_Information We Collect Passively._**

  * We use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to do such things as track information about your use of the Website on an aggregate and anonymous basis so that we may recognize you and your device and improve the Website.
  * **_Cookies in General._** A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your computer or mobile device from the Website, and is stored in your computer or mobile device. The Website requires the use of cookies.
  * **_Third-Party Cookies_**. We may also engage third parties, such as DoubleClick, Facebook, Taboola, AdSense, Yarrp, and Revcontent (the “Third Parties”) to track and analyze data from the Website. In this case, we will use the data collected by the Third Parties to help us administer and improve the quality of the Website, and to analyze usage. The Third Parties use cookies (the “Third Parties’ Cookies”) to assist us in offering the Website and serving advertisements based on your prior visits to the Website. The Third Parties’ Cookies, such as the DoubleClick cookie, enable the Third Parties to serve advertisements to you based on your visits to the Website and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie or other Third Parties’ cookies for interest-based advertising. Please visit http://www.aboutads.info/ to learn how to opt out of Third Parties’ Cookies.

2\. How We Use The Information We Collect

We use the Personal Information we gather about you for the following reasons:

  * To provide the Website; to communicate with you about the Website or changes to the Terms and Privacy Policy; to respond to inquiries; and for other customer service purposes.
  * To personalize and customize the Website to better suit your preferences, to offer personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise improve your experiences with the Website.
  * For marketing and promotional purposes. We may collect Personal Information about you to send you special offers and promotions, or to otherwise contact such users about products or information we think may be of interest. You may opt out of these offers and promotions by emailing us at the email address listed below.
  * To improve the Website, and for other research and analytical purposes.

3\. How We Share Your Information

We pride ourselves on honesty and transparency. We may disclose the Personal Information that it collects in the ways described above, and to comply with the law, and to protect us and other users of our Website. For example, we may share information with:

  * **_Third-Party Providers._** To help run the Website, we may disclose the Personal Information we collect from you to third-party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents.
  * **_Business Mergers_**. If we are bought out by or merged with another company, or we are involved in a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the Personal Information we have collected from you to the other company.
  * **_In Response to Legal Process_**. We may disclose the Personal Information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process.
  * **_To Protect Us and Others_**. We reserve the right to disclose Personal Information gathered from you if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of the Terms or this Privacy Policy, or in the course of litigation which we are a party.
  * **_Aggregate and De-Identified Information_**. We reserve the right to share aggregate or de-identified information about its users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research, or similar purposes.

4\. Third-Parties

We may use several third-party services and applications to help run the Website, evaluate usage of the Website, improve the Website, customize user experiences, and for advertising purposes. These entities may use cookies and Personal Information shared in the manner described in their own Privacy Policy to perform their services. These third parties include advertising networks, secure credit card and e-commerce processing, account analytics, and storage and security companies. The following third-parties may collect Personal Information through the Website:

  * Facebook, https://www.facebook.com/policy.php
  * DoubleClick, http://www.google.com/doubleclick/
  * Taboola, http://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy
  * AdSense, https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/1348695?hl=en
  * Yarrp, http://www.yarpp.com/privacy-policy
  * Revcontent, http://revcontent.clickbooth.com/support/solutions/articles/159621-revcontent-publisher-terms-conditions

5\. Third-Party Links

The Website may contain links to third-party websites and/or applications (the “Third-Party Links). Any access to and use of such Third-Party Links is not governed by this Privacy Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those Third-Party Links. We are not responsible for the information practices of such Third-Party Links.

6\. User Content

If you post content using the Website, all of the information that you post will be made available to the public. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy. As a result, you should never post any sensitive information using the Website that you are not comfortable sharing with the public. We are not liable to you or any other person for any content or information you post using the Website, or the use or disclosure of such content or information by other users or third parties.

7\. Security of Your Personal Information

We have implemented a variety of security measures to protect the Personal Information that we collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security. You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, phone, and computer by, among other things, keeping your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity via unauthorized password activity.

8\. Access to Your Personal Information

You may modify the Personal Information that you have submitted by logging into your account and updating your profile information.

You may also view and delete your Account History, which includes the browsing history and analytics data we have collected about you. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified, or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of our systems for a period of time.

9\. Do Not Track Signals and Minors

We do not respond to Do Not Track Signals.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13. The Website and its features are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at the email address, below.

10\. Contact Us

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Website or would like to make a complaint, please contact us at contact@sktmarketing.com

11\. Changes to This Policy

This Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We reserve the right to change this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Policy at www.allthingsceleb.com If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the Personal Information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on www.allthingsceleb.com.
